Hello friends, now we will talk about III
Lord General Insurance Company Limited,
whose quarterly results have been
declared by the company. So let's check
friends, how are the quarterly results of the company,
but before that, let's check
some fundamentals of the company. If friends talk about the
market cap of the company, then the
market cap of the company is 96497 crores, which is
a large cap company, friends. After this,
friends, if we talk about the
price to earnings ratio of the company, friends, it is
38.3, so on seeing friends, the valuation of the company
seems to be correct, but still we
will check
where the valuation of the company stands in comparison with its PE. After this,
friends, let's talk about the
return on capital employed of ROI, friends, it is
22.5, which is a very
good ROI, after that, friends, let's talk about the
return on invested
capital, friends, it is 22.5, which is a very
good ROI, after this,
friends, let's talk about the promoter holding,
friends, the promoter holding is 51.6, which
friends  There is a good promoter holding.
After this, if we talk about public
holding, then the public holding is
6.91, which is a very good
public holding. After this, if we talk about
debt to equity ratio, then the debt to
equity ratio is 0.0. So, friends, there is
no debt of any kind on the company and the company is a debt-free
company. So overall, friends, if we talk about the
fundamentals of the company, then the fundamentals of the company are
very good.
Friends, let us see where the valuation of the company
stands in comparison to the top companies of its sector. If friends
talk about life insurance, its PE
ratio is 13.04. If friends talk about
SBI Life Insurance, its PE ratio is
64.0. If friends talk about HDFC Life
Insurance, its PE ratio is
79.100300, which last year was 212653. This year it has
increased to 2811. So friends,
this is also a good thing for the company. So
finally, friends, let us move on to the
quarterly results of the company and see what happens today.  The
company has presented its quarterly results here.
How is the company's performance in it? If friends talk about sales, then
in the last quarter, friends, the company had
made sales of Rs 6147 crore, which has
increased to Rs 6161 crore in this quarter.
So, quarter by quarter,
friends, the company has
shown growth in sales here. After this, friends, if we talk about
net profit, then in the last quarter,
friends, the company had
generated a net profit of Rs 694 crore, which has become a
net profit of Rs 724 crore in this quarter.
Friends, let's talk about the
year-on-year quarterly result and let's see
how is the company's performance here.
If friends talk about sales, then
in the same quarter last year, friends, friends, the company had made
sales of Rs 5194 crore, which has
increased to Rs 6161 crore in this quarter. So,
if friends
talk about sales, then there has been growth quarter on
quarter as well as year
on year. Quarterly, the company has
shown growth in sales here. After that,
friends, let's talk  If we talk about net profit, then
in the same quarter last year, friends, the company had
generated a net profit of Rs 431 crore,
which has become a net profit of Rs 724 crore in this quarter this year. So,
if friends talk about net profit,
then there is growth here quarter on quarter as well as
year on year. The
company has shown growth here quarterly. So, if
friends talk about the company's quarter three
results, then the company has
presented a very good and positive result for the company here. After this,
friends, if we talk about cash flow, then the cash flow
operating activity cash flow has almost always been
positive for the company and
even after March 2024, the company's cash flow operating activity
cash flow is running positive, which is a
very
good thing for the company. After this, friends, if we talk about the
share holding pattern, then the promoters'
holding friends, there is
no mention of any share holding
pattern of this quarter here, but we take a look at the last to last quarter.
If friends talk about
promoter holding, then the promoter holding
friends was 51.8 in the last quarter,
which is 51.8 in this quarter.  It has reduced to 51.6 here,
so friends the promoters' holding has
reduced slightly here, which is
not a good thing for investors.
After that, friends, if we talk about public
holding, then friends the public holding
was at 717 in the last to last quarter, which
reduced to 6.91 in the last quarter, so
friends here the public holding has
reduced quarter by quarter, so
friends this is a good thing for investors. So
friends, this was the quarter three
result of III Labad General Insurance Company
Limited. Rest, how did you like my video,
you can tell us in the comment section.
If friends, you liked the video, then
like my video and
if you want the results of future quarters too, then
subscribe to my channel. Thank you very much.